<house>
    <player>
        <inventory items=""/>
        <room name="unknown room"/>
        <memories memory=""/>
        <computer used="False"/>
        <score val="0"/>
    </player>
    <intro>
    Consciousness slowly returns to you after a very unnatural slumber. You feel your eyes open as panic sends your mind
    into an adrenaline fueled search of your last memory. You take deep breaths trying to calm yourself from the
    initial flood of panic. As your mind races you slowly come to terms that you have no recollection of the events that
    transpired before you woke. In fact, you fail to remember anything. Your eyes dart around the room in an attempt to
    find some kind of solution to the riddle of where and who you are.
    </intro>
    <title>
                                         ___  ___    ___  __       ___   _
                                        |#|_  |#|   |#|_  \#\  /  |#|_  |#|\ |
                                        |#|_  |#|_  |#|_   \#\/   |#|_  |#| \|
    </title>
    <tip>
   ------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
    TIP:  You can type 'menu' to see a list of commands, 'inv' to see what items are in your inventory, 'memories' to see
          what you've remembered, 'score' to see your current score, 'save' to save game, and 'exit' to quit.
   ------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
    </tip>
    <room name="unknown room">
        <desc>     The room is completely foreign to you.  There's no telling how long you've been unconscious. Days? Weeks?
     Months?  You're uncertain.  The only choice you have is to try to find answers.  Try to find a way out.  The
     truly unfortunate thing is that your capabilities are rendered.  You only know how to look, open, and take
     the artifacts around you.  The first thing you do is carefully inspect your surroundings.  There's a bookshelf,
     the bed that you woke up on, a large metal door, and a desk.
        </desc>
        <l>You notice that the room is furnished with dusty antiques.  The only light source is coming from thin
                      paneled windows with bars on them.  You take a moment to get more familiar with the room you're in.</l>
        <o>You go to the metal door and try to escape.  To no surprise, the metal door is locked.  For a moment you
              contemplated the possibility of the windows being a way out.  It's not long before you realize that even if
              you got the bars off, you wouldn't fit through the tiny slit anyway.  Ultimately, your attempts to open the
              room have failed.</o>
        <t>Knowing how to perform only three actions must be taking it's toll on your intelligence.  After hours of
               struggling with your pockets you finally come to the conclusion that your pants were made too tight to fit a
               room inside of them. You give up, and stop trying to take the room.</t>
        <item type="desk" obtainable="0" inspected="0">
            <score point="1" on="l desk">
                <prompt>                   &lt;You've added a memory to your memory bank, and earned a point.&gt;</prompt>
                <memory>The impossible shape drawn on the desk's layer of dust.</memory>
            </score>
            <visible in="unknown room"/>
            <l> The desk is aged and brittle probably made out of wood.  You're afraid to touch it in fear it might fall
                   apart.  Dust and thick spiderwebs are covering the surface.  It must have been here for a long time to
                   collect that much buildup.  You start to fade away into a daydream, and for a moment everything goes black.
                   When the light reappears, you notice you've drawn a symbol into the dust.  It's impossible.
                                                                ____
                                                               /.../\
                                                              /.../##\
                                                             /.../####\
                                                            /.../######\
                                                           /.../###/\###\
                                                          /.../###/  \###\
                                                         /.../###/\   \###\
                                                        /.../###/  \   \###\
                                                       /.../###/    \   \###\
                                                      /.../###/      \   \###\
                                                     /.../###/        \   \###\
                                                    /.../###/          \   \###\
                                                   /.../###/            \   \###\
                                                  /.../###/______________\   \###\
                                                 /........................\   \###\
                                                /..........................\   \###\
                                                -----------------------------   \###/
                                               \                                 \#/
                                                \_________________________________/
            </l>
            <o> You hesitated for a moment because the thing feels unsteady.  The last thing you want is for it to fall
               apart.  Whoever has kept you here might be upset.  Who DOES have you here, you wonder.  Eventually you
               opened the drawers slowly as the desk trembled.</o>
            <t>Your attempts are futile, poor thing.  The second you got your arms around it the whole thing shifted and
               almost fell on top of you.  You're lucky you're still alive.</t>
            <item type="mirror" obtainable="1" inspected="0">
                <visible in="desk"/>
                <score point="3" on="l mirror">
                    <prompt>                     &lt;You've gained another memory.&gt;</prompt>
                    <memory>Alice is your mother.</memory>
                </score>
                <l>You stare into the mirror wishing you knew who the woman staring back at you is.  You remember your face
                    but the things you don't remember still outweigh the few that you do.  After carefully inspecting the mirror,
                    you notice the name "Alice" engraved on the back.  A memory comes back to you.  Your mother's name is
                    Alice.
                </l>
                <o>The mirror is of little use.</o>
                <t>You hope that having the mirror in your inventory will help you.</t>
            </item>
            <item type="journal" obtainable="1" inspected="0">
                <visible in="desk"/>
                <requirement req="key">
                    <prereq>&lt;The journal is locked.  You must find the key to unlock it.&gt;</prereq>
                </requirement>
                <l> The journal is old, falling apart at its seams.  You don't remember having seen this item before, but
                      you're eyes are focused on the symbol engraved in the leather.  It appears to be the as the one that
                      appeared on the desk.</l>
                <o>You started to go through the journal and saw a lot of meaningless things written.  It seems like the
                 owner was a scientist of sorts.  It wasn't until you got to the last page that you saw something
                 interesting.  It reads,

                                                "WANT OUT OF HERE?
                                                 Use this:

                                                 { m b w y m f e n }"
                </o>
                <t>You take the journal hoping it will help lead to answers.</t>
                <item type="picture" obtainable="0" inspected="0">
                    <visible in="journal"/>
                    <l> Your gaze focused in on the picture attached to the mirror on the desk. There's a man, a woman,
                      and a little boy posing for a happy picture. Unfortunately, you don't know who the two boys are.
                      At that moment you recall seeing your reflection in the window.  It wasn't long before you
                      realized that the woman in the picture is me. You took a moment to inspect the picture further
                      and found something strange on the back. There is a small note stuck to it.
                    </l>
                    <o> You try to use the picture in an futile attempt to spark some memories.  The attempt was ultimately
                  unsuccessful.</o>
                    <t>You could take the picture with you, but it's really not necessary so you leave it behind.</t>
                    <item type="note" obtainable="1" inspected="0">
                        <visible in="picture"/>
                        <score point="2" on="l note">
                            <prompt>                   &lt;You've added a memory to your memory bank.&gt;</prompt>
                            <memory>You remember an irrational date:  March 14, 1915</memory>
                        </score>
                        <l>You look at the note stuck to the back of the picture with speculation.  Why did someone
                  put it in a locked journal on the back of a picture?  Clearly, it was meant to stay hidden.
                  Regardless, you read the note.  It reads,
                           
                                           "March 14, 1915"

                  The date rings a bell to you.  You're not sure if it is someones birthday or just a date you happen
                  to remember.  It certainly is an irrational date.
                        </l>
                        <o>What are you trying to do?  Don't cause anymore trouble for yourself.  Try not to destroy the
              owner's belongings.</o>
                        <t>You carefully detach the note from the picture, and place the note in your pocket.</t>
                    </item>
                </item>
            </item>
        </item>
        <item type="bed" obtainable="0" inspected="1">
            <visible in="unknown room"/>
            <l> Knowing that the bed is where you woke, you decide inspecting it is a good idea. After thorough inspection
                  you realize the bed is just an ordinary antique bed, but it is hiding something.</l>
            <o> You contemplate going to sleep, but decide against it in fear of forgetting everything you've remembered so far.</o>
            <t>There is no reason for you to do this.</t>
            <item type="pillow" obtainable="0" inspected="0">
                <visible in="bed"/>
                <score point="2" on="l pillow">
                    <prompt>                     &lt;You've gained a memory.&gt;</prompt>
                    <memory>Purple is your favorite color.</memory>
                </score>
                <l> The pillow looks dingy, yet it is still soft and fluffy. It has a purple pillowcase on it -
                     your favorite color.
                </l>
                <o> You take the pillowcase off and look anything that could be hidden inside.</o>
                <t>You could take the pillow with you, but it's really not necessary so you leave it behind.</t>
                <item type="cloth" obtainable="1" inspected="0">
                    <visible in="pillow"/>
                    <requirement req="o pillow">
                        <prereq>&lt;That item is unreachable.&gt;</prereq>
                    </requirement>
                    <score point="3" on="l cloth">
                        <prompt>                    &lt;You've gained another memory.&gt;</prompt>
                        <memory>The keyword is SALT.</memory>
                    </score>
                    <l>Inspecting the cloth shows that it was written on in the past with what appears to be faded
                   permanent marker. It took some time but eventually you were able to make out what it says,

                                                  "KEYWORD = SALT"
                    </l>
                    <o>You can't do that.</o>
                    <t>You think this will help you.</t>
                </item>
            </item>
            <item type="mattress" obtainable="0" inspected="0">
                <visible in="bed"/>
                <l>You look at the mattress wondering how much time you spent laying on it. You can see the indentation
                      of where your body used to lay for hours on end. How many hours was it, you wonder?
                </l>
                <o> You lift the mattress off the box spring looking for anything you can find.</o>
                <t>You try to take the mattress off the bed, but fail miserably.</t>
                <item type="key" obtainable="1" inspected="0">
                    <visible in="mattress"/>
                    <requirement req="o mattress">
                        <prereq>&lt;That item cannot be found.&gt;</prereq>
                    </requirement>
                    <l>
                                                     _
                                                    /o \_____
                                                    \__/-="="`

                        You don't know what it opens, but it's got to open something.</l>
                    <o>The key cannot be opened.</o>
                    <t>You hold on to the key hoping to find what it unlocks.</t>
                </item>
            </item>
            <item type="lock" obtainable="0" inspected="0">
                <visible in="bed"/>
                <requirement req="book">
                    <prereq>&lt;You must have the item with the combination in it.&gt;</prereq>
                </requirement>
                <l>

                                                       .-""-.
                                                      / .--. \
                                                     / /    \ \
                                                     | |    | |
                                                     | |.-""-.|
                                                    ///`.::::.`\
                                                   ||| ::/  \:: ;
                                                   ||; ::\__/:: ;
                                                    \\\ '::::' /
                                                     `=':-..-'`

                    You exam the lock. It has a circular dial with numbers ranging from one to 30. Currently, the lock won't budge.</l>
                <o> With the combination securely in your inventory, you carefully turn the dials to the correct number double checking
               yourself with each turn.  After entering the last digit, you pull the lock open revealing the now unlocked chest.</o>
                <t>The lock is attached to the safe which cannot be obtained.  Thus, you cannot take the lock, but you effort remains
               valiant.</t>
                <item type="safe" obtainable="0" inspected="0">
                    <visible in="lock"/>
                    <requirement req="o lock">
                        <prereq>&lt;You look around the room, but cannot remember where it is.&gt;</prereq>
                    </requirement>
                    <l>Upon inspection, you realize that the safe is embedded in the wall, and it's seemingly impossible to remove.
                  You wonder who would go through so much effort to keep things locked and hidden in walls.  The person wasn't very
                  clever to leave the combination in the same room.
                    </l>
                    <o> Since you've opened the lock, you can open the chest.  You pull the safe open, revealing items that intrigue you.
               Surely there's something with answers inside.</o>
                    <t>The safe is securely embedded in the wall.  Even though you would like to keep it, it's not yours to keep.</t>
                    <item type="photo album" obtainable="0" inspected="0">
                        <visible in="safe"/>
                        <requirement req="o safe">
                            <prereq>&lt;You cannot get to that item at the moment.&gt;</prereq>
                        </requirement>
                        <score point="3" on="l photo album">
                            <prompt>                          &lt;You've gained another memory.&gt;</prompt>
                            <memory>The gold engravings on the photo album.</memory>
                        </score>
                        <l>You look at the photo album, and blow off the dust build-up. Underneath all the
                         dust, you see a beautiful leather cover with gold engravings.  These gold engravings
                         make you have a flashback of your childhood.   You remember seeing this album before
                         as a child.  Someone was showing it to you and telling you of its importance.  The
                         words were soft and muffled.  You can't decipher whether or not it's male or female,
                         young or old, or anything else.  All you know is this album is important.
                        </l>
                        <o> You open the photo album and see old fashioned pictures of people you've never seen
                      before.  Among the pages of antique photos, you stumble upon something interesting.
                      Maybe this will assist you decrypt encrypted phrases.</o>
                        <t>You don't need to take the album with you so you leave it behind.</t>
                        <item type="decryption table" obtainable="1" inspected="0">
                            <visible in="photo album"/>
                            <requirement req="o photo album">
                                <prereq>&lt;You must open the photo album first.&gt;</prereq>
                            </requirement>
                            <l>
                                 | A B C D E F G H I J K L M N O P Q R S T U V W X Y Z
                                ======================================================
                                A| b c d e f g h i j k l m n o p q r s t u v w x y z a
                                B| c d e f g h i j k l m n o p q r s t u v w x y z a b
                                C| d e f g h i j k l m n o p q r s t u v w x y z a b c
                                D| e f g h i j k l m n o p q r s t u v w x y z a b c d
                                E| f g h i j k l m n o p q r s t u v w x y z a b c d e
                                F| g h i j k l m n o p q r s t u v w x y z a b c d e f
                                G| h i j k l m n o p q r s t u v w x y z a b c d e f g
                                H| i j k l m n o p q r s t u v w x y z a b c d e f g h
                                I| j k l m n o p q r s t u v w x y z a b c d e f g h i
                                J| k l m n o p q r s t u v w x y z a b c d e f g h i j
                                K| l m n o p q r s t u v w x y z a b c d e f g h i j k
                                L| m n o p q r s t u v w x y z a b c d e f g h i j k l
                                M| n o p q r s t u v w x y z a b c d e f g h i j k l m
                                N| o p q r s t u v w x y z a b c d e f g h i j k l m n
                                O| p q r s t u v w x y z a b c d e f g h i j k l m n o
                                P| q r s t u v w x y z a b c d e f g h i j k l m n o p
                                Q| r s t u v w x y z a b c d e f g h i j k l m n o p q
                                R| s t u v w x y z a b c d e f g h i j k l m n o p q r
                                S| t u v w x y z a b c d e f g h i j k l m n o p q r s
                                T| u v w x y z a b c d e f g h i j k l m n o p q r s t
                                U| v w x y z a b c d e f g h i j k l m n o p q r s t u
                                V| w x y z a b c d e f g h i j k l m n o p q r s t u v
                                W| x y z a b c d e f g h i j k l m n o p q r s t u v w
                                X| y z a b c d e f g h i j k l m n o p q r s t u v w x
                                Y| z a b c d e f g h i j k l m n o p q r s t u v w x y
                                Z| a b c d e f g h i j k l m n o p q r s t u v w x y z
                            </l>
                          <o>You can't do that.</o>
                          <t>You want to keep this with you in case you ever need to decrypt something.</t>
                        </item>
                    </item>
                    <item type="handle" obtainable="1" inspected="0">
                        <visible in="safe"/>
                        <requirement req="o safe">
                            <prereq>&lt;You can't get to that item yet.&gt;</prereq>
                        </requirement>
                        <l>This handle looks like it has fallen off of something like a drawer or cabinet.</l>
                        <o>You twist and turn the handle trying to open it while making sure it doesn't open 
                or have any surprises hidden inside.</o>
                        <t>Maybe the broken remains will be needed to open something.</t>
                    </item>
                </item>
            </item>
        </item>        
        <item type="bookshelf" obtainable="0" inspected="0">
            <visible in="unknown room"/>
            <l> Amongst the crowd of books on the bookshelf, one stands out. Your eyes are drawn to one specific book.</l>
            <o> After inspecting the bookshelf, you notice that there's a gap between it and the wall behind. You slide
                    your fingers as far in between as possible. On the very tips of your fingers you feel an edge on the wall.</o>
            <t>The bookshelf cannot be removed from the hinges attached to the wall.</t>
            <item type="door" obtainable="0" inspected="0">
                <visible in="bookshelf"/>
                <requirement req="o bookshelf">
                    <prereq>You need to open the bookshelf first.</prereq>
                </requirement>
                <l>
                                                 __________
                                                |  __  __  |
                                                | |  ||  | |
                                                | |  ||  | |
                                                | |__||__| |
                                                |  __  __()|
                                                | |  ||  | |
                                                | |  ||  | |
                                                | |  ||  | |
                                                | |  ||  | |
                                                | |__||__| |
                                                |__________|

                   The door was carefully hidden by the bookshelf.  There must be something valuable behind it.
                </l>
                <o>You open the door and walk into the secret room.</o>
                <t>The door cannot be removed from the wall.</t>
            </item>
            <item type="book" obtainable="1" inspected="0">
                <!--Book contains memory, gives more insight about who she is-->
                <visible in="bookshelf"/>
                <score point="2" on="l book">
                    <prompt>                   &lt;You've gained another memory.&gt;</prompt>
                    <memory>Your mother reading to you before bedtime.</memory>
                </score>
                <l>The name of the book is "Alice in Wonderland" by Lewis Carrol. Well, if you're Alice, you're
                  certainly not in Wonderland.  You don't think you're Alice... at least not that Alice.
                  You remember a time when your mother used to read it to you before bedtime.
                  Your eyes stop at your favorite part:

                    ========================================================

                    'It is a long tail, certainly said Alice, looking down
                    with wonder at the Mouse's tail; 'but why do you call it
                    sad?' And she kept on puzzling about it while the
                    Mouse was speaking, so that her idea of the tale was
                    something like this:- 'Fury said to a
                                       mouse, That
                                         he met in the
                                              house, "Let
                                                  us both go
                                                     to law: I
                                                     will prosec-
                                                      cute you --
                                                    Come, I'll
                                                 take no de-
                                             nial: We
                                         must have
                                     the trial;
                                   For really
                                 this morn-
                               ing I've
                              nothing
                             to do."
                              Said the
                               mouse to
                                the cur,
                                 "Such a
                                   trial, dear
                                       sir, With
                                          no jury
                                           or judge,
                                               would
                                            be wast-
                                         ing our
                                      breath."
                                    "I'll be
                                  judge,
                               I'll be
                             jury,"
                            said
                           cun-
                           ning
                             old
                              Fury;
                                "I'll
                                  try
                                    the
                                     whole
                                      cause,
                                       and
                                     con-
                                   demn
                                 you to
                              death"
                    ========================================================

                </l>
                <o>You flip through the pages stopping at your favorite parts.  The pictures intrigue you since you haven't
              seen them in however many years.  'How many years has it been?', you wonder.  As you're about ready to close
              the book, you notice that on the front of the cover there is a handwritten message.  It reads,

                                     "start 7 - right 17 - left 13 - left 27 - right 29"

              This looks like the combination to a lock. </o>
                <t>This book is a memento. You want to keep it.</t>
                <!--<item type="page" obtainable="1" inspected="0">-->
                    <!--<visible in="book"/>-->
                <!--&lt;!&ndash;The page in the book has a picture of a sequence of shapes used-->
                    <!--to open something in the room behind&ndash;&gt;-->
                    <!--<requirement req="o book">-->
                        <!--<prereq>&lt;You must open the book first.&gt;</prereq>-->
                    <!--</requirement>-->
                    <!--<l>FILL</l>-->
                    <!--<o>FILL</o>-->
                    <!--<t>FILL</t>-->
                <!--</item>-->
            </item>
            <item type="box" obtainable="0" inspected="0">
                <visible in="bookshelf"/>
                <requirement req="screwdriver">
                    <prereq>&lt;You need to have a screwdriver in your inventory to open this box.&gt;</prereq>
                </requirement>
                <l>The box is wooden and looks to be hand made.</l>
                <o> You use the screwdriver to remove the screws one by one.</o>
                <t>The box would only take up space in your inventory.</t>
                <item type="badge" obtainable="1" inspected="0">
                    <visible in="box"/>
                    <l>It looks like some sort of security badge. There's no distinguishable words on it, but there is an
                   oddly familiar symbol colorfully printed on it.</l>
                    <o>You notice there's a small indentation along the perimeter of the badge. You think about trying
               to take the thing apart but decide against it. It's of more use in one piece.</o>
                    <t>You slide the badge in your back pocket.</t>
                </item>
            </item>
        </item>
        <item type="metal door" obtainable="0" inspected="0">
            <visible in="unknown room"/>
            <special/>
            <requirement req="badge, computer_used">
                <prereq>&lt;You desperately wiggle the knob, but the door does not open.&gt;</prereq>
            </requirement>
            <l>You look at the metal door and thoroughly inspect it.  It appears that the door's locks are electronic.
                        There's something that looks like a slot for a digital badge.  Also, there's a type-pad with the numbers 0-9.
                        You wonder if you'll be clever enough to hack your way out.</l>
            <o>After obtaining the badge, and entering the password, you hear a loud noise.  The large metal locks have
                     been released.  Hesitantly, you open the door.  </o>
            <t>There's no way to take the metal door.</t>
        </item>
        <exit link="door" to="secret room"/>
        <exit link="metal door" to="living room"/>
    </room>
    <room name="secret room">
        <!--Special: "cutscreen" into next room.  Items from other room can't be seen
            or interacted with.  Change game state.-->
        <desc>
        You've entered the secret room where everything is different.  In the room before, everything was antique,
        dusty, and meek.  In here, it looks like a high-tech operations area.  Nothing in the room is dusty or meek.
        In fact, it's quite shiny and clean.  It appears as though this room has been maintained while you were "away".
        There are things in the secret room that beg for your attention.
        </desc>
        <!--<visible in="bookshelf"/>-->
        <!--<requirement req="o door">-->
            <!--<prereq>&lt;You cannot find that item.&gt;</prereq>-->
        <!--</requirement>-->
        <l>You slowly walk around the perimeter of the room taking note of everything you see.  Immediately, you feel
                      more comfortable in this room than the other.  In here, it's not so dreary.</l>
        <o>Opening the room is unfeasible.
        </o>
        <t>This simply isn't going to happen.</t>
        <item type="entrance" obtainable="0" inspected="0">
            <visible in="secret room"/>
            <l>The entrance leads back to the secret room where you came from.</l>
            <o>Entering unknown room...</o>
            <t>The entrance can't be detached from the wall.</t>
        </item>
        <item type="painting" obtainable="0" inspected="0">
            <!--Painting has numbers on it for opening the box-->
            <visible in="secret room"/>
            <score point="5" on="l painting">
                <prompt>                       &lt;You've gained another memory.&gt;</prompt>
                <memory>Your mother painting the artwork in the secret room.</memory>
            </score>
            <l>
                                            ,--._                      _
                                            "'.  '.                  ,';
                                               )   '.              ,' /
                                             _/      '.          ,'   '.
                                           -"__        '.;  /  ,`'    ,-`
                                               \        /  ( ,===.  _`. )
                                               /__      `.__//.' \\/_.-`
                                                  '-,._.-    \ \_/\\ ,-.
                                                      \.-     /  \_\\/||
                                                     _/\\    :o o :-'/;.`.
                                                  _,";-,;|   :/"\ : // ||))
                                             _..."((|_//||-.._\"//  `` ;;''
                                            /,-----"||" ''    \`._
                                           //      ,'|         `-.`-..._
                                          ::     ,','             '.__.=
                                          ::     |||  _
                                           \\_   ""   ))     'Beware the jabberwock'
                                            \_"--....';
                                              '""---"'

                       When you look at the painting on the wall, you begin to daydream.  You remember a time when you were laying
                       in bed, wrapped in your favorite blanket while your mother was on the opposite side of the room painting
                       and your father was reading you "Alice in Wonderland".
            </l>
            <o>You lift the painting from the wall to see if there's anything hidden behind.  You're shocked when you
                  find out there's nothing there.</o>
            <t>As much as you'd love to take the painting with you, you decide against it.  Hauling it around in your
                   inventory may damage it's beauty.</t>
        </item>
        <item type="couch" obtainable="0" inspected="0">
            <visible in="secret room"/>
            <l>

                                                 .-="""""""""""=-.
                                                 | . . . . . . . |
                                                 | .'.'.'.'.'.'. |
                                                ()____ _____ ____()
                                                ||____I_____I____||
                                                ||_______________||
                                                W                 W

                    The couch is large and comfortable.  It's made with fine brown leather.
                    Why that many people would be in the secret room, you don't know.  Nonetheless, the couch is a nice piece
                    of furniture.</l>
            <o> The couch is to heavy for you to lift so you get on the floor and look for anything underneath.  There's
                nothing underneath, but you see some other things.</o>
            <t>The couch is too heavy to take.</t>
            <item type="blanket" obtainable="1" inspected="0">
                <visible in="couch"/>
                <score point="6" on="l blanket">
                    <prompt>                      &lt;You've gained two new memories.&gt;</prompt>
                    <memory>The blanket from your childhood.  Your father's death.</memory>
                </score>
                <l>You look at the blanket and remember everything about it.  You got it when you were just a child from
                     your grandmother.  She knitted it for your fifth birthday.  Since the moment you got it, you always slept
                     with it.  After your father died, you would wrap yourself in this blanket for comfort.
                </l>
                <o>You use the blanket by wrapping it around yourself.  When you do so, you don't feel so alone and
                 confused.  In fact, for a moment you feel at ease.</o>
                <t>You take the blanket along with you in case you get cold.</t>
            </item>
            <item type="cushion" obtainable="0" inspected="0">
                <visible in="couch"/>
                <l>The cushions are nothing special.  You notice that the cushions can be removed from the couch.</l>
                <o> You lift the cushions from the couch searching for something hiding in the couch cushions.</o>
                <t>There's really no reason for you to do that.</t>
                <item type="screwdriver" obtainable="1" inspected="0">
                    <visible in="cushion"/>
                    <requirement req="o cushion">
                        <prereq>&lt;There is no screwdriver in sight.&gt;</prereq>
                    </requirement>
                    <l>
                                                                       ____________________________
                                     _____                           ,\\  ___________________      \
                                    |      `------------------------' || (___________________)     `|
                                    |_____.------------------------._ ||   ____________________     |
                                                                     `//__(____________________)___/

                        At first look, the screwdriver is a disappointment.  Then you think of all the uses a screwdriver
                        can have.</l>
                    <o>The screwdriver cannot be opened.</o>
                    <t>You decide it may be useful to take the screwdriver with you.</t>
                </item>
            </item>
        </item>
        <item type="cabinet" obtainable="0" inspected="0">
            <visible in="secret room"/>
            <requirement req="handle">
                <prereq>&lt;The cabinet is missing its handle. Try opening it once you have the handle in your inventory.&gt;</prereq>
            </requirement>
            <l>You look at the cabinets and realize there's nothing special about them.  The only thing that looks out of
                     the ordinary is the handle that has been fiddled with.</l>
            <o> You attach the handle to the cabinet door and open it to see what's inside.</o>
            <t>The cabinet cannot be taken with you.</t>
            <item type="manual" obtainable="1" inspected="0">
                <visible in="cabinet"/>
                <requirement req="o cabinet">
                    <prereq>&lt;You must open the cabinet first.&gt;</prereq>
                </requirement>
                <l>The manual looks like it's for the computer on the table.</l>
                <o> You open the manual and scan the pages for any useful information.  There's a certain page that sticks
                 out to you.  This page looks like instructions for how to decrypt the encrypted message.</o>
                <t>You take the manual with you in case you need it while operating the computer.</t>
                <item type="recipe" obtainable="1" inspected="0">
                    <!--Instructions on how to decrypt the cipher-->
                    <visible in="manual"/>
                    <requirement req="o manual">
                        <prereq>&lt;You need to open the manual first.&gt;</prereq>
                    </requirement>
                    <l>You look at the recipe and realize that it is not for humans to read, but for the computer.</l>
                    <o>There's nothing in the recipe for you to use or open.</o>
                    <t>The recipe may be useful at some point so you decide to take them with you.</t>
                </item>
            </item>
        </item>
        <item type="table" obtainable="0" inspected="0">
            <visible in="secret room"/>
            <l>The table is much newer than the things in the other room.  It's made of high quality wood with live edges.</l>
            <o> You try to lift the table off the ground, but it's of no use.  The table is too heavy.</o>
            <t>There's no way you'll be able to carry the table.</t>
            <!--<item type="newspaper" obtainable="1" inspected="0">-->
                <!--&lt;!&ndash;Newspaper leads to great insight about who she is, when it is, and how long she's been there&ndash;&gt;-->
                <!--<visible in="table"/>-->
                <!--<score point="10" on="l newspaper">-->
                    <!--<prompt>&lt;You've gained an important memory.&gt;</prompt>-->
                    <!--<memory>TBD</memory>-->
                <!--</score>-->
                <!--<l>FILL</l>-->
                <!--<o>FILL</o>-->
                <!--<t>FILL</t>-->
            <!--</item>-->
            <item type="computer" obtainable="0" inspected="0">
                <!--Special:  Password?-->
                <visible in="table"/>
                <special/>
                <!--<requirement req="o table">-->
                    <!--<prereq>You try to use the computer, but it asks for a password before you can do anything.</prereq>-->
                <!--</requirement>-->
                <l>You don't know what a computer is or what it does.</l>
                <o> </o>
                <t>In order to take the computer with you, you'd have to unplug all the cables.  Not only that, where
                   would you keep it?  You move on without taking the computer.</t>
            </item>
        </item>
        <exit link="entrance" to="unknown room"/>
    </room>
    <room name="living room">
        <desc>
        You insert your badge into the metal door and watch as it slowly grinds open.  A bright light catches your eye
        as it disappears down a long tunnel.  As the light fades from sight you feel a sudden shift in gravity.  Without
        warning you are now falling down the tunnel towards the light that holds the truth...

        Suddenly, you hit the ground with a loud THUD.  You stand up, and dust yourself off.  When you look around your
        memory comes back to you.  You're not Alice, no. But your mother is.  You've been trapped in this house directly
        above Wonderland by your mom's nemesis.  They've been holding you hostage for ELEVEN years, but you've never aged.

        Now that you have the answers, you're nothing more than confused.  There's nowhere else for you to go but back up
        to the room you just escaped.  And just like that symbol you've seen around the room, everything seems impossible.
        </desc>
    </room>
</house>



